export class Preguntas {
    
    data: any= new Array();
    questions = [
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:1,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Gustavo Fring",
            optionB: "Domingo Molina",
            optionC: "Todd Alquist",
            optionD: "Jesse Pinkman",
            correctOption: "optionD"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:2,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Carmen Molina",
            optionB: "Skyler White",
            optionC: "Brock Cantillo",
            optionD: "Lydia Rodarte-Quayle",
            correctOption: "optionB"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:3,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Andrea Cantillo",
            optionB: "Jane Margolis",
            optionC: "Carmen Molina",
            optionD: "Skyler White",
            correctOption: "optionD"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:4,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Walter White",
            optionB: "Jesse Pinkman",
            optionC: "Henry Schrader",
            optionD: "Todd Alquist",
            correctOption: "optionC"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:5,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Skyler White",
            optionB: "Jane Margolis",
            optionC: "Brock Cantillo",
            optionD: "Marie Schrader",
            correctOption: "optionD"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:6,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Mike Ehrmantraut",
            optionB: "Skyler White",
            optionC: "Anna Gunn",
            optionD: "Dean Norris",
            correctOption: "optionA"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:7,
            question: "¿Quien es este personaje?",
            optionA: "Anna Gunn",
            optionB: "Skyler White",
            optionC: "Marie Schrader",
            optionD: "Dean Norris",
            correctOption: "optionC"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:8,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Gustavo Fring",
            optionB: "Henry Schrader",
            optionC: "Mike Ehrmantraut",
            optionD: "Jesse White",
            correctOption: "optionA"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:9,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Mike Ehrmantraut",
            optionB: "Brandon Mayhew",
            optionC: "Steve Gomez",
            optionD: "Hector Salamanca",
            correctOption: "optionD"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:10,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Mike Ehrmantraut",
            optionB: "Brandon Mayhew",
            optionC: "Hector Salamanca",
            optionD: "Domingo Molina",
            correctOption: "optionD"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:11,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Steven Gomez",
            optionB: "Domingo Molina",
            optionC: "Tuco Salamanca",
            optionD: "Gustabo Fring",
            correctOption: "optionC"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:12,
            question: "¿Quien es este personaje?",
            optionA: "Marco & Leonel Salamanca",
            optionB: "Lydia Rodarte-Quayle",
            optionC: "Todd Alquist",
            optionD: "Jane Margolis",
            correctOption: "optionA"
        },
    
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:13,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Jane Margolis",
            optionB: "Lydia Rodarte-Quayle",
            optionC: "Carmen Molina",
            optionD: "Andrea Cantillo",
            correctOption: "optionB"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:14,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Gale Beotticher",
            optionB: "Sauld Godman",
            optionC: "Mike Ehrmantraut",
            optionD: "Todd Alquist",
            correctOption: "optionD"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:15,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Jane Margolis",
            optionB: "Carmen Molina",
            optionC: "Andrea Cantillo",
            optionD: "Skyler White",
            correctOption: "optionA"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:16,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Theodore Beneke",
            optionB: "Barndon MayHew",
            optionC: "Skinny Pete",
            optionD: "Todd Alquist",
            correctOption: "optionC"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:17,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Brandon Mayhew",
            optionB: "Skenny Pete",
            optionC: "Brandon Mayhew",
            optionD: "Huell Babineaux",
            correctOption: "optionA"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:18,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Saul Godman",
            optionB: "Skenny Pete",
            optionC: "Brandon Mayhew",
            optionD: "Huell Babineaux",
            correctOption: "optionC"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:19,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Saul Godman",
            optionB: "Skenny Pete",
            optionC: "Brandon Mayhew",
            optionD: "Steven Gomez",
            correctOption: "optionD"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:20,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Theodore Beneke",
            optionB: "Barndon MayHew",
            optionC: "Todd Alquist",
            optionD: "Walter White",
            correctOption: "optionA"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:21,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Tuco Salamanca",
            optionB: "Henry Schrader",
            optionC: "Theodore Beneke",
            optionD: "Gale Boetticher",
            correctOption: "optionD"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:22,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Lydia Rodarte-Quayle",
            optionB: "Andrea Castilllo",
            optionC: "Carmen Molina",
            optionD: "Marie Scharder",
            correctOption: "optionB"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:23,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Steven Gomez",
            optionB: "Brock Cantillo",
            optionC: "Domingo Molina",
            optionD: "Tuco Salamanca",
            correctOption: "optionB"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:24,
            question: "Este personaje es: ?",
            optionA: "Lydia Rodarte-Quayle",
            optionB: "Skler White",
            optionC: "Carmen Molina",
            optionD: "Andre Cantillo",
            correctOption: "optionC"
        },
    
        {   
            img : "",
            questionNumber:25,
            question: "Este personajes es: ?",
            optionA: "Lydia Rodarte-Quayle",
            optionB: "Skler White",
            optionC: "Carmen Molina",
            optionD: "Andrea Castillo",
            correctOption: "optionC"
        }
    
    ]
    constructor(){
            
    }

    cargarData(data:any){
        
        this.data = data;        
        var next = 1;

        for (var q of this.questions) {
            for (let i = 0; i < this.data.length; i++) {
                    if (q.questionNumber == next && next < this.data.length) {
                        
                        q.img = this.data[next].img;

                        switch (q.correctOption) {
                            case "optionA":
                                q.optionA = this.data[next].name;
                                break;
                            case "optionB":
                                q.optionB = this.data[next].name;
                                break;
                            case "optionC":
                                q.optionC = this.data[next].name;
                                break;
                            case "optionD":
                                q.optionD = this.data[next].name;
                                break;            
                        
                            default:
                                break;
                        }
                        next++;
                    }
            }        
    }
}
    
}
